gardenia.net 2018-11-01

# Privacy

_**Last updated: June 2018**_

_**1\. Introduction**_

_Jardins Sans Secret, LLC_   _(_ “ **us** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **our** ”, or the “ **Company** ”) respects our customers and understands that you are concerned about privacy. We have posted this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to let you know what kind of information we collect, how it is handled and with whom it may be shared. As we continue to develop our website (“ **Site** ”) and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we offer, we will update this Policy to inform you of changes that make impact your personal information. We encourage you to refer to this Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand the current policies that apply to the information you provide to us. Any updates to this Policy will be prominently displayed on our Site, [Gardenia.net](https://www.gardenia.net/).

**2\. Applicability of this Privacy Policy**

This Policy applies to information collected through our **Site**. Although the Site may provide links to third-party Sites, such third-party Sites are not covered under this Policy. We provide these links for your convenience only and we assume no responsibility for the privacy or security of information that you provide to any third-party through linked Sites or any other means. “ **Third-Parties** ” mean any person or entity other than us and you.

**3\. Information We Collect**

We collect non-personally identifiable information from you during the course of your visit to our Site. This information may include general information regarding your Internet Service Provider and host, your IP address, the content on the Site you access, the platform operating system and web browser you use, and the date, time, and duration of your visit to the Site.

This information may be collected through the use of a “cookie.” Cookies are small text files that are stored on your hard drive to store your preferences. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. You can choose to refuse any cookie by following the procedure suggested by your particular web browser. You may delete Company cookies from your computer, but doing so may impair your use of the Site.

Company may also use “web beacons” on the Site from time to time. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on a web page to track or monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page.

Company may also use certain statistical analysis services, such as Google Analytics, to generate statistics in the aggregate about visitors to the Site. Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“ **Google** ”). Google Analytics uses cookies to analyze how users use the Site.

Company may also collect information from you through your voluntary submission. For instance, such information may be submitted through your use of an online form to register with Company to access and use certain portions of the Site, or by sending Company an email to request certain services from Company. You may also give Company personal information when submitting a résumé and/or an employment application. In other cases, such information may be the content or information you post in a web-forum, in a chat room, or through other interactive or “social networking” portions of the Site (collectively referred to herein as the “ **Interactive Portions** ” of the Site). The information you voluntarily submit may include information which may be used to personally identify you, such as your name, physical address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, and/or tax identification number.

**4\. How**   **Company**   **Uses the Information It Collects**

Company uses information it collects to, among other things, process your requests and transactions, offer or furnish additional services, personalize the types of information you receive from Company, assess trends in the use of the Site, develop content and functionality that helps serve our users needs, and improve the services Company provides. Any information you submit using the Interactive Portions of the Site, even personally-identifiable information, may be automatically publicly displayed on the Site. You therefore should be very careful about providing any personally identifying information using the Interactive Portions of the Site.

Company’s use of the non-personally-identifiable information it collects through the Site is unrestricted. Company may sell or license non-personally-identifiable information or aggregated information (information derived from personally-identifiable information, but not containing any personally identifying details) to Third Parties.

In the event Company uses Google Analytics, the information generated by the cookie about your use of the Site (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Site, compiling reports on website activity for Company and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

Company will not use your personally-identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection (the “ **Purpose** ”) without first attempting to notify you via the last e-mail address Company has in its records. Company will only share your personally-identifiable information with Third Parties that assist Company in carrying out the Purpose. Such Third Parties shall be required to use your personally-identifiable information only to assist in the Purpose and to maintain the confidentiality of your personally-identifiable information. Résumés and other materials submitted by job applicants are used for applicant screening and hiring purposes, and for general human resource related purposes.

Company reserves the right at all times to: (a) use disclose any information it reasonably believes necessary to satisfy any law, regulation, government request, court order, subpoena or other legal process; (b) edit or remove any information, in whole or in part, that in Company’s sole discretion is objectionable, disruptive to the Site or in violation of the Terms and Conditions; (c) use and disclose any information when Company believes it is necessary to prevent harm or injury, to prevent fraud, or to protect Company’s legal interests; and (d) use and disclose any information in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

Company may also transfer personal information in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets, or otherwise undergo a change in control. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

If you reside in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, you may opt out of some of the disclosures described in this section by contacting us as set forth below.

**5\. Retention and Integrity of Information**

Company retains personal and non-personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, and may retain it for a longer period of time if required or permitted by law.

You can request access, modifications to, or removal of the personal information collected by Company through your use of the Site by contacting Company using the contact point set forth below. To honor your request, Company will need the exact information you want to access, modify, or remove. Company will use reasonable efforts to provide you with access to and to modify or remove such information if requested, provided, however, Company will not be liable to you should it be unable, after such efforts, to identify, modify, or remove such information. Company may also decline requests that are unreasonable, require disproportionate technical effort, or that jeopardize the privacy of others. Due to the dynamic and ever-changing nature of the interactive portions of the Site, you acknowledge and agree it may be impossible for Company to access, modify or remove your personal information from these portions of the Site.

**6\. Children**

Company is committed to protecting the privacy of children. Neither Company nor any of its services are designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. Company does not collect personally-identifiable information from any person that Company knows to be under the age of 13.

**7\. Security**

Company has put in place reasonably appropriate physical, electronic, and/or procedural safeguards using a risk-based approach to protecting your personally-identifiable information. However, even with such measures, no one is able to guarantee that unauthorized Third Parties will not be able to bypass these measures or otherwise capture such information. Company shall not be liable to you for any Third Party’s unauthorized access to or use of your personally-identifiable information.

**9\. Contact Us**

Please contact Company to learn more about its privacy practices or to change your privacy choices:

_Jardins Sans Secret, 210 East 61st street, New York, NY 10065, USA_

_Email: privacy@gardenia.com_

**10\. Privacy Statement for Data Subjects Whose Personal Information May Be Collected in or from the EEA**

While customers who are located in the EEA are customers of our U.S. entity, we recognize and, to the extent applicable to us, adhere to relevant EEA data protection laws.

**11\. Collection and Transfer of Data Outside the EEA**

In the course of providing our services, we may incidentally collect personal information from individuals or “Data Subjects” who reside in the European Union (EU) or European Economic Area (“EEA”). In order to facilitate the access to services we provide to customers located in the EEA, we request explicit consent for the transfer of personal information from the EEA to the U.S. If you are an individual located in the EEA and you decline to consent to such transfer, you will no longer be able to use our services.

**12\. Lawful Grounds to Process and Obtain Consent**

We process the personal information of Data Subjects who are located in the EEA for one or more of several lawful purposes, including:

  * With your explicit consent: 
    * To provide you with our services, including customer service support;
    * To optimize and enhance our services for all customers or for you specifically;

Data Subjects in the EEA may withdraw consent at any time where consent is the lawful basis for processing their personal information. Should a Data Subject withdraw consent for processing or otherwise object to processing that impedes our ability to comply with applicable laws and regulations, a Data Subject may be unable to avail him or herself of the services we provide.

**13\. Automated Decision-Making**

We do not engage in automated decision-making.

**14\. Non-Disclosure of Personal Information**

Our employees are prohibited, either during or after their employment, from disclosing personal information to any person or entity outside of our company, including family members, except under the circumstances described above. An employee is only permitted to disclose the personal information of a customer to such other employees who need access to such information in order to deliver our services to that customer.

**15\. Our Contact Information for Persons Located within the EEA**

If you are located in the EEA or Switzerland and have questions or concerns regarding the processing of your personal information, you may contact us at: _privacy@gardenia.com_ ; or write to us at:

_Jardins Sans Secret_

_210 East 61st Street_

_New York, NY 10065, USA_

If, as an EEA Citizen, you believe that we have not adequately resolved any such issues, you have the right contact your local EU supervisory authority.
